

MUHAMMAD MUSTAQEEM

UI/UX DESIGN





ABOUT US

Hey I'm a ui/ux designer engineer with great of experience in understanding and designing digital products from concept ideas to production. I work with my clients to help them create web apps and mobile apps from the ground up or to help them solve business problems through visual and usability improvements.

- **■** 03067101225, 03423510876
- ☐ m-mustaqeem@outlook.com
- Ahad Heights gulberg III lahore

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

— 2014 - 2018

Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan

FSC PRE ENGINEERING

— 2011 - 2014

B.I.S.E FSD

CERTIFICATIONS

GOOGLE UX DESIGN

coursera online Cources
Dec 2021 to May 2022

UI/UX DESIGNER

Treehouse online Cources
Jan 2019 to July 2019

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Treehouse online Cources
May 2019 to July 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

TOTAL 3+ YEARS

UX Consultant Citrok Lahore — Feb 2022 · Presen . 5 mos

In my position in the company as a UX consultant, I work on different kinds of products like CMS, SAAS, App design, and website + responsive solutions.

UX Designe Thinkdone solutions — May 2020 - Jan 2022 · 1 yr 9 mo

My position in the company was as a senior UI/UX designer, I did many projects like Elevatyx website design + wireframe, Kelger Management website design+Develop Front end only, DrGlow website, MFC App, and KFC App

UI/UX Designe

Xaavia Studios Lahore — Sep 2019 - Mar 2020 · 7 mos

joined the company as a UI/UX Designer. I designed and created a complete professional branding suite for one of their client mentioned as Blackstone including the logo, Website design, Marketing material, and Application graphics as well. I also designed the entire wireframe of the Text Neck App launched by Moltyfoam and Burnsroad House Website.

UI/UX Designe

Bitsclan Solution Lahore — Apr 2019 - Sep 2019 - 6 mos

After 3 months I was promoted to UI/UX designer. I designed a Urtasker website, which was an e commerce solution, I also designed the wireframe as well as the entire design. Including some marketplace websites and wireframe designs.

Graphic Designer

Bitsclan Solution Lahore — Feb 2019 - Apr 2019 · 3 mos

I will join this company as a Junior Graphic designer, I did many projects like logo designing, banner animation, etc.

SKILLS





